domainnamenews.com 2011-11-01

# Privacy Policy | Domain Name News (DNN)

Privacy Policy for www.domainnamenews.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.domainnamenews.com/contact "contact us") by email at editor@domainnamenews.com.

At www.domainnamenews.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.domainnamenews.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.domainnamenews.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
www.domainnamenews.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our [advertising](http://www.domainnamenews.com/advertising "advertising") partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense. Users may opt out of the use of the Google DART cookie[ by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.domainnamenews.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.domainnamenews.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.domainnamenews.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Information collected by third-parties.**

We may allow third-party companies that use tracking technologies, such as cookies or pixels, to record IP information about users who visit or interact with our website. Our website does not provide any personal information to these third parties. This information allows them to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Some of these third-party advertising companies may be advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising Initiative which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting from member companies.
